Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
- Recordings
  - GSS (6), 05/07/1986; gss_343; Recording of various performances of mixed chorus, sopranos and baritones.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)
    601-604: "Hallelujah" (mixed chorus); 605: "Turn to God" (mixed chorus); 606-609: "Humming Section" (mixed chorus); 609-612: "Turn to God" (mixed chorus); 613: ‘It is good that man" (mixed chorus); 614-616: ? (mixed chorus); 617: "Sing praises" (sopranos, baritones)
  - GSS (7), 05/07/1986; gss_344; Recording of mixed choruses.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)
    701-708: "Sing ye praises" (mixed chorus); 720-723: "Oh my God" (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (8), 05/08/1986; gss_345; Recording of choruses performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)
    101-117: (chorus); 118: "poverty..." (soprano, mixed chorus, percussive effects)
  - GSS (1), 05/23/1986; gss_146; Additional notes by the audio engineer read: "mixed chorus".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 11)
  - GSS (2), 05/23/1986; gss_147; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 11)
  - GSS (3), 05/23/1986; gss_148; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Ros. and mixed choir. G. S. talks about reimbursement checks, etc. with members".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 11)
  - GSS (1), 01/19/1987; gss_331; Recording of chorus, piano, soprano solo, song in German.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 29)
    101: ? (Gerry is the pianist, piano, soprano solo); 102-118: song in German (chorus, piano, soprano solo)
  - GSS (2), 01/19/1987; gss_332; Recording of German songs with piano, mixed chorus, soprano solo.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 29)
    201-206/213-218: cont'd from 331: German lyrics (piano, mixed chorus, soprano solo); 207-212: (piano, mixed chorus)
  - GSS (3), 01/19/1987; gss_333; Recording of German lyrics with piano, soprano solo.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 29)
    cont'd from 332: 301-314: German lyrics (piano, soprano solo)
  - GSS (4), 01/19/1987; gss_038; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Soprano with piano, choir mixed. "Gory" is the pianist."; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS (5), 01/19/1987; gss_334; Recording of German lyrics with chorus, soprano, piano; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 29)
    Cont'd from 333: 501/508-521: German lyrics (chorus, soprano, piano); 502-507: German lyrics (soprano solo, piano)
  - GSS (6), 01/19/1987; gss_335; Recording of chorus accompanied with piano and no accompaniment, some German lyrics.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 29)
    Cont'd from 334: 601-607: German lyrics (chorus, unaccomp.); 607-613: German lyrics (chorus, piano); 614-616: "Golden light" "My lady sleeps" "Dreams of a summer night"; 617-618: madrigal form "Happiness be crowned" (chorus)
  - GSS (7), 01/19/1987; gss_336; Recording of unaccompanied chorus.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 29)
    Cont'd from 335: 701-703: madrigal form "Happiness be crowned" (chorus); 704-711: "La la la la ..." as the Swingle singers wold do it (chorus)
  - GSS (8), 01/19/1987; gss_337; Recording of chorus performances with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 29)
    801: "Do wah, do be do" incorporated "Clair de Lune" (chorus, piano); 802: (chorus)
  - GSS (1), 01/26/1987; gss_039; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Brass trio or quartet with chorus (mixed)".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS (2), Jan 26-27 [1987]; gss_144; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 11)
    201-216: Trumpet, bassoon; "Christmas Eve" (mixed choir in French); 217: Bassoon, trumpet duet (trio?), choir in French
  - GSS (3), Jan 26-27 [1987]; gss_145; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 11)
    101: Piano, violin; 301: French singing, mixed choir; 302: trumpet; 303: French singing choir; bassoon, trumpet
  - GSS (4), Jan 26-27, 1987 [?]; gss_041; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS (5), 01/26/1987; gss_042; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS (6), 01/26/1987; 01/27/1987; gss_043; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS (7), 01/27/1987; gss_044; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS (8), 01/27/1987; gss_045; Notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "All instrumentals. French and English spoken".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS (9), 01/27/1987; 01/28/1987; gss_046; Notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "French, English spoken vocals in French", Faure?, Gabriel".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS (10), 01/28/1987; gss_047; Notes by the audio engineer RJH read: " GSS speaks French. Instrumental with vocals, chorus in French, Faure?, Gabriel".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS (11), 01/28/1987; gss_329; Recording unaccompanied chorus and instrumental music: trumpets, oboe, with conversations in French.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 29)
    1101-1109: "Shenandoah" (chorus, unaccomp.); 1110-1117: "Povane" by Faure (instrumental, trumpets, oboe, conversations in French)
  - GSS (12), 01/28/1987; gss_330; Recording of rhythmic singing in French, with orchestra, soprano, alto, bass, tenor,ensemble, chorus.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 29)
    1201: (talk); 1202-1215: rhythmic singing in French "Ba, de, da, ba ,de ,do" (orchestra, soprano, alto, bass, tenor, ensemble, chorus)
  - GSS (13), 01/28/1987; gss_584; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - GSS (14), 01/28/1987; gss_585; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - GSS (15), 01/28/1987; 01/29/1987; gss_569; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 46)
  - GSS (16), 01/29/1987; gss_570; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 46)
  - GSS (17), 01/29/1987; gss_571; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 46)
  - GSS (18), 01/29/1987; gss_572; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 46)
  - GSS (19), 01/29/1987; 01/30/1987; gss_573; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 46)
  - GSS (20), 01/30/1987; gss_574; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 46)
  - GSS (21), 01/30/1987; gss_575; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 46)
  - GSS (22), 01/30/1987; gss_576; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 46)
  - GSS (1), 02/02/1987; gss_326; Recording of mixed chorus unaccompanied and accompanied, piano, hand bells, whistling.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 29)
    101-106: "Swanee river" (chorus, unaccomp.) ("Old folks at home", "Oh Darling" replaces "darkies" - to the better men of the sons); 107: "Universe..." (mixed chorus, piano, hand bells, whistling, soloists)
  - GSS (2), 02/02/1987; gss_327; Note on the box reads: "Early 2's missing on cassette thru 204 (big)". Recording of mixed chorus, piano, hand bells, whistling, discussions.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 29)
    Cont'd from 326: 201-214
  - GSS (3), 02/02/1987; gss_040; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS (4), 02/02/1987; gss_328; Recording of piano mixed chorus.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 29)
    401-406: "Da da da de de de" (piano mixed chorus); 407-416: "Da da da de de de" and "Clair de Lune" incorporated (piano mixed chorus)
  - GSS (1), 02/16/1987; gss_386; Recording of mixed chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    101-109: "Jill thinks, Jack thinks..." (mixed chorus); 110-123: "Jack is afraid of Jill..." (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (2), 02/16/1987; gss_387; Recording of chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    Cont'd from 386: 201-108: "Jack is afraid of Jill..." (chorus); 209-212: "She want him to want her" (Jack and Jill) (chorus); 213-222: "want to be wanted" (Jack and Jill) (chorus); 223-226: "Jill wants Jack to want" (chorus)
  - GSS (3), 02/16/1987; gss_388; Recording of mixed chorus, soloists and duets performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    Cont'd from 387: 301-307: "Jack and Jill" (chorus, soloists); 308: "If I don;' know I don't know..." (soloists duet); 309-311: "I think I don't know..." (soloists duet)
  - GSS (4), 02/16/1987; gss_389; Recording of tenors, sopranos performance without accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    401-407: "If I don;' know I don't know..." (tenors, sopranos, unaccomp.); 408-414: "They are playing a game..." (tenors, sopranos, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (5), 02/16/1987; gss_390; Recording of Orchestra, women's and men's choruses performance with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    501-506: (Orchestra); 507-508: "When I came to my senses..." (women chorus); 509-513: (women chorus); 514-516: (mixed choruses)
  - GSS (6), 02/16/1987; gss_391; Recording of Orchestra, women's and men's choruses performance with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    Cont'd from 390: 601-617: (Orchestra, choruses)
  - GSS (7), 02/16/1987; gss_392; Recording of Orchestra, choir performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    Cont'd from 391: 701: (Orchestra); 702-706: "When two couples are in love..." (Orchestra, choir); 707-712: "Surprise..." (Orchestra, choir); 713-722: (Orchestra, choir)
  - GSS (1), 02/17/1987; gss_382; Recording of choruses performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    101-103/106: "This cornfield..." (chorus); 104-105/111: "Shall I not rejoice" (chorus); 107-109/115-118: "Me as the principal..." (chorus); 110: "These beans..." (chorus); 112-114: "At the abundance..." (chorus); 119-123: "The grass veins" (women's choir, men's choir,mixed choirs)
  - GSS (2), 02/17/1987; gss_383; Recording of chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    201"The Symbol of perpetual youth" (chorus); 202: "Note Yellow but green..." (chorus); 203-206: "Returning sun..." (chorus); 207-214: "Ribbon..." (chorus); 215-223: "From..." (chorus); 224: "The grass grains..." (chorus); 225-228: "Infinite faith and promise..." (chorus); 229: "moderation" (chorus); 230: "If I could be intoxicated" (chorus)
  - GSS (3), 02/17/1987; gss_384; Recording of chorus performance with comments by Gregg Smith.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    301: "Only if I could be intoxicated" (chorus); 302-305: "New day" (chorus); 306-309: "On hope..." (chorus); 310-313: "I don't think ..." (chorus, spoken lyrics and whispering); 314-315: "Imagine yourself..." (chorus); 316: "Yourself alone in the world..." (chorus); 318/320-322: "The morning..." (chorus); 319/323-324: "Everywhere: (chorus); 325-326: "The morning wind..." (chorus); 327: "Complete performance" says Gregg Smith
  - GSS (4), 02/17/1987; gss_385; Recording of soloists and chorus performance with conversations at the end.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    401-403/405-406: "Come let us..." (soloists and chorus); 404: "Ting, ting, ting" (soloists and chorus)
  - GSS (1), 05/11/1987; gss_393; Recording of soprano, chorus with no accompaniment, piano.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    101-124: "The Creation: "In the beginning (Roz - soprano, Gerry - pianist, chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (2), 05/11/1987; gss_394; Recording of soprano and chorus.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    Cont'd from 393: "In the beginning": 201-204: "Haven..." (soprano, chorus); 205-212/214: "One place" (soprano, chorus); 213/215-216:"And it was said..." (soprano, chorus); 217-224: "And the evening and the morning" (soprano, chorus)
  - GSS (3), 05/11/1987; gss_395; Recording of soprano and chorus.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    Cont'd from 394: 301-308: "And the evening and the morning" (soprano solo - Roz., chorus); 309-316: "And the evening and the morning" (chorus); 317-322: "And God saw that it was good..." (soprano solo -Roz., chorus)
  - GSS (4), 05/11/1987; gss_396; Recording of chorus and soprano.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    Cont'd from 395: 401-404/407-410: "And God said..." (chorus); 405-406: "And God said..." (chorus, soprano); 411: "be fruitful and multiply..." (chorus, soprano); 412-416: "dominion..." (chorus, soprano); 417-420: "which is upon the face..." (chorus, soprano); 421-429: "In the beginning..." (Roz solo -- soprano)
  - GSS (5), 05/11/1987; gss_397; Recording of chorus and soprano.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    Cont'd from 396: 501-503: "Things that move upon the earth..." (soprano solo, chorus); 504-505: "Where there is life..." (soprano solo, chorus); 506-508: (soprano solo, chorus); 509-511: "He resembled the 7th day..." (soprano solo, chorus); 512: "And God blessed the 7th day..." (soprano solo, chorus); 514-518: "He hath made..." (soprano solo, chorus)
  - GSS (6), 05/11/1987; gss_398; Recording of soprano and chorus.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    Cont'd from 397: 601-617: (soprano, chorus)
  - GSS (7), 05/11/1987; gss_019; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "acapella mixed choir"; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 4)
  - GSS (8), 05/11/1987; 05/12/1987; gss_399; Recording of chorus performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    801-813: (chorus)
  - GSS (9), 05/12/1987; gss_400; Note on the box reads: "Need cassette". Recording of chorus and soprano solos performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    901-902: "From..." (chorus); 903-905: "Oh Lord..." (chorus); 906: "Lord hear my prayer" (chorus); 907: "The voice of my complaint..."; 907-920: "O my dear heart..." (chorus, soprano solo)
  - GSS (10), 05/12/1987; gss_401; Recording of chorus and soprano solos performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    Cont'd from 400: 1001: "O my dear heart..." (chorus, soprano); 1002-1005: "Praise be God eternality" (chorus, soprano); 1006-1017: Latin (chorus, soprano); 1018: "Oh my God..." (chorus, soprano)
  - GSS (11), 05/12/1987; gss_402; Recording of chorus and soprano solos performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    Cont'd from 401: 1101-1120: All the same piece(unaccomp. chorus, sopranos)
  - GSS (12), 05/12/1987; gss_403; Recording of chorus, soprano performances and the George Gershwin's piece "By Strauss".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    Cont'd from 402: 1201-1206: "Oh my God" (chorus); 1207-1212: "By Strauss" George Gershwin, Ira (piano, soprano, chorus); 1213: pick up
  - GSS (13), 05/12/1987; gss_404; Recording of chorus, piano, soprano performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    No slate between songs: 1301: "By Strauss", George Gershwin, (soprano, piano, chorus)
  - GSS (14), 05/12/1987; gss_405; Recording of chorus, piano, soprano performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 32)
    1401-1405: "By Strauss" (soprano, piano, pickup)
  - GSS (1), 12/07/1987; gss_123; Note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Gloria..." (mixed chorus, unaccompanied, Latin?); GSS explains the process and "overhangs" for newcomers".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 9)
  - GSS (2), 12/07/1987; gss_067; Note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Christmas music: Caroler's song, (mixed chorus, unaccompanied); "Loudu..."; "Hallelujah"; "Bethlehem".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 9)
  - GSS (3), 12/07/1987; gss_124; Note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Christmas music".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 9)
    301-306: "Bethlehem" (mixed choir, unaccompanied); 307-309: "A. C. I. E."; 310-313: "A Tiny babe..."; 314: "Star..."; 315-319: "On this Day..." (piano accompanied)".
  - GSS (4), 12/07/1987; gss_125; Note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Tests"; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 9)
    401 - mixed choir with piano; 202 - in Latin "Hosanna in exchelsis; 403 - 404: "Dora nobis pacem", mixed choir with piano".
  - GSS (1), 01/21/1988; gss_064; Note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Spiritual medley, mixed chorus, rhythm section, piano; acapella insert; spirituals with acapella insert; song about singing music".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 9)
  - GSS (2), 01/21/1988; gss_562; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 45)
  - GSS (3), 01/21/1988; gss_563; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 45)
  - GSS (4), 01/21/1988; gss_564; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 45)
  - GSS (5), 01/21/1988; gss_565; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 45)
  - GSS (6), 01/22/1988; gss_066; Note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "How does your garden grows..." (mixed chorus, unaccompanied); "O, So scary"; "growing room"; "See how they grow".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 9)
  - GSS (7), 01/22/1988; gss_126; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 9)
    701-710: "when I sing a 12 tone row..." (piano, mixed chorus); 711: (tenors, mixed choir); 712: "With the blessing of Almighty God" (mixed choir); 713: "It's A wrap".
  - GSS (1), 02/15/1988; gss_127; Note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Tones at head. Dennis is the organist; Bob's Comments [?]".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 9)
    101-115: "Hosanna in the highest" (choir, pipe organ, soprano [Ros], tenors); 116-117: "And he said unto them"
  - GSS (2), 02/15/1988; gss_128; Note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Mixed choir, pipe organ, soprano, tenors".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 9)
    201: "it is written..."; 202-203: "The people..."; 205-209: "For his was the spirit of God"; "Hosanna in the highest"; 210-213: "With whom"; 214-217: "When roses fade"; 218-220: "Pg. 3 - Mary a rose"
  - GSS (3), 02/15/1988; gss_129; Note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Mixed chorus, soprano, piano".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 9)
  - GSS (1), 03/07/1988; gss_586; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - GSS (2), 03/07/1988; gss_587; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - GSS (3), 03/07/1988; gss_588; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - GSS (4), 03/07/1988; gss_065; Note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "in madrigal style, women unaccompanied; hammering".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 9)
  - GSS (5), 03/07/1988; gss_589; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - GSS (6), 03/07/1988; gss_583; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 43)
  - GSS (4), 05/15/1988; gss_130; Note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Mixed chorus, baritones, women mixed chorus, tenors, soprano".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 9)
    401: "To them and me"; 402-403: "Ah - To them..."; 403-407; 409: "Fired the shot heard around the world"; 408: "World..."
  - GSS (1), 11/07/1990; gss_528; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 42)
  - GSS (2), 11/07/1990; gss_529; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 43)
  - GSS (3), 11/07/1990; gss_530; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 43)
  - GSS (4), 11/07/1990; gss_013; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH read: "Geronimo", mixed chorus acapella".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 2)
  - GSS (5), 11/07/1990; gss_531; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 43)
  - GSS (6), 11/07/1990; gss_532; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 43)
  - GSS (7), 11/07/1990; gss_533; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 43)
  - GSS (8), 11/07/1990; gss_534; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 43)
  - GSS (1), 03/11/1991; gss_518; Recording of soprano solos and chorus performances in Latin.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 41)
    100/105: chanting in Latin (solo soprano); 101-104: chanting in Latin (chorus); 105: -113: (chorus)
  - GSS (2), 03/11/1991; gss_519; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 42)
  - GSS (3), 03/11/1991; gss_520; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 42)
  - GSS (4), 03/11/1991; gss_521; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 42)
  - GSS (5), 03/11/1991; gss_014; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 2)
  - GSS (6), 03/11/1991; gss_522; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 42)
  - GSS (1), 03/26/1991; gss_523; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 42)
  - GSS (2), 03/26/1991; gss_524; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 42)
  - GSS (3), 03/26/1991; gss_525; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 42)
  - GSS (4), 03/26/1991; gss_526; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 42)
  - GSS (5), 03/26/1991; gss_527; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 42)
  - GSS (1), 05/18/1992; gss_476; Recording of chorus performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 38)
    101-104: "Kansas" (chorus); 105-119: (chorus)
  - GSS (2), 05/18/1992; gss_477; Recording of chorus performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 38)
    Cont'd from 476: 201-220: (chorus)
  - GSS (3), 05/18/1992; gss_478; Recording of chorus performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 38)
    301-327: (chorus)
  - GSS (4), 05/18/1992; gss_479; Recording of chorus, acapella performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 38)
    401: "Of indecision" (chorus, acapella); 402-403: "Why don't they answer..." (chorus, acapella); 404-410: "Missed it" (chorus, acapella); 411-416: "Serves you right" (chorus, acapella)
  - GSS (5), 05/18/1992; gss_480; Recording of chorus, acapella performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 38)
    Cont'd from 479: 501-50: "They refuse to answer" (chorus, acapella); 504-505: "Oh, I wish" (chorus, acapella); 506-508: "What a mess" (chorus, acapella); 509-511: "I wish I'd never been born" (chorus, acapella); 512: ‘Fool that I am" (chorus, acapella); 513: "But thank God" (chorus, acapella); 515: "Amen" (chorus, acapella)
  - GSS (6), 05/18/1992; gss_481; Recording of chorus in French and English, acapella performances with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 38)
    Cont'd from 480: 601-602: "Amen" (chorus, acapella); 603-610: "Autumn leaves" (chorus in French and English, acapella)
  - GSS (7), 05/18/1992; gss_482; Recording of chorus in French and English, acapella performances with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 38)
    Cont'd from 481: 701-7110: "Autumn leaves" (chorus in French and English, acapella)
  - GSS (8), 05/18/1992; gss_483; Recording of chorus in French, acapella performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 38)
    Cont'd from 482: 801: (chorus in French, acapella)
  - GSS (1), 10/26/1992; gss_513; Recording of mixed chorus performance in Spanish with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 41)
    101-109: Spanish lyrics (piano, mixed chorus)
  - GSS (2), 10/26/1992; gss_514; Recording of mixed chorus performance in Spanish with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 41)
    Contd. from 513: 201-210: Spanish lyrics (piano, mixed chorus)
  - GSS (3), 10/26/1992; gss_515; Recording of mixed chorus performance in Spanish with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 41)
    Contd. from 514: 301-314: Spanish lyrics (piano, mixed chorus)
  - GSS (4), 10/26/1992; gss_016; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 2)
  - GSS (5), 10/26/1992; gss_516; Recording of mixed chorus performance in Spanish with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 41)
    Contd. from 515: 501-509: Spanish lyrics (piano, mixed chorus)
  - GSS (6), 10/26/1992; gss_517; Recording of mixed chorus performance in Spanish with piano accompaniment and comments; accapella performance in English.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 41)
    601-604: Spanish lyrics (piano, mixed chorus); 605-612: "Come let us hymn our hymn to Rease" (mixed chorus, accapella, sings as a round)
  - GSS (1), 3/8/1993; gss_448; Recording of mixed chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 35)
    101-109: (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (2), 3/8/1993; gss_449; Recording of mixed chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 35)
    Cont'd from 448: 201-213: (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (3), 3/8/1993; gss_450; Recording of mixed chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 35)
    Cont'd from 449: 301-311: "Lord have mercy" (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (4), 3/8/1993; gss_451; Recording of mixed chorus with percussion performance with discussions.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 35)
    Cont'd from 450: 401-414: (mixed chorus, noises, percussion)
  - GSS (5), 3/8/1993; gss_452; Recording of ethereal sounds and noises, men's and women's choruses, tenor soloists, with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 35)
    Cont'd from 451: 501-514: (ethereal sounds and noises, men's and women's choruses, tenor soloists)
  - GSS (6), 3/8/1993; gss_453; Recording of noises, choir and choral humming/ harmonies performances.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 36)
    601--602: (noises); 603-606: (noises, choir, choral humming/ harmonies)
  - GSS (7), 3/8/1993; gss_454; Recording of mixed chorus performances with conversations at the end.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 36)
    701-711: "Lo le lo le lea oh" (mixd chorus)
  - GSS (1), 3/9/1993; gss_455; Recording of piano, chorus, soprano performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 36)
    101: (piano, chorus, soprano); 102-109: (women's section", piano)
  - GSS (2), 3/9/1993; gss_456; Recording of piano, men's chorus, antiphonal men's chorus, women's choir and soprano solos with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 36)